[](javascript:void();)

Privacy Policy
==============

#### BillGO, Inc. Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: June 15, 2023**

_[Our previous Privacy Policy may be viewed here](https://billgo.com/privacy-policy-old?hsLang=en)._ 

BillGO, Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries, including BillGO MT, Inc. (“BillGO”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through the practices set forth in this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and disclose personal information in connection with one or more of the websites owned or operated by BillGO or its subsidiaries that link to this Privacy Policy (each, a “Website” and collectively, the “Websites”), the Prism mobile application (the “App”), our social media pages, our email and other communications, and our other products, services, and events (collectively, the “Services”).

**Please note, you may also use BillGO’s products and services through your mobile banking app, an online banking portal, or through a relationship with another provider of financial services and products. In those cases, please refer to the privacy policies of your financial institution or product provider.**

This Privacy Policy covers the following topics:

* * Updates to this Privacy Policy
    * Personal Information We Collect
    * Use of Personal Information
    * Sharing of Personal Information
    * Links to Other Sites and Services
    * Your Choices
    * Children
    * Security
    * Transfer of Personal Information
    * For Nevada Residents
    * For Vermont Residents
    * For California Residents
    * Contact Information

**Updates to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy was last changed on the “Last Updated” date set forth at the top of this Privacy Policy.  We are constantly improving our Services, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will alert you to material changes by making updates to this page, placing a notice on a BillGO product/service home page or webpage, within the App, or by notifying you by electronic means (such as email, text notification or notification to your Services account).  In addition, we will also edit the date at the top of this Privacy Policy to reflect the date of the changes.  If you use the Services after any changes to this Privacy Policy have been posted, you agree to all the changes.  

**Personal Information We Collect**

The table below describes the categories of personal information (with non-exhaustive examples) that we may collect about you:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Categories** | **Examples** |
| A. Individual Identifiers | **Contact information**, such as first and last name, postal address, email address, account name or username, phone number, and social media handle.<br><br>**Online identifiers**, such as Internet Protocol (IP) address, device ID, and other identifiers.<br><br>**Government identification numbers**, such as Social Security number, driver’s license number, state ID card number, tax ID, or passport number. |
| B. Financial Information | **Payment and billing information**, such as debit or credit card number or financial account details. |
| C. Precise Geolocation | **Real-time location data**, if you provide permission via the App. |
| D. Audio Data | **Customer service call recordings**, recorded for training and quality assurance purposes. |
| E. Commercial Information | **Account information**, such as your log-in credentials, date of birth, information that you store in your profile, and other details about your use of the Services.<br><br>**Order history**, such as records of products and services you have purchased from us.<br><br>**Transaction and billing data**, such as payment amounts and payment methods used to complete transactions, bank account information for settlement, and other relevant information about the financial institutions you use to conduct business.<br><br>**Preferences**, such as any preferences you set in your account and any marketing or communications preferences.<br><br>**Survey responses**, such as information about your background and use of or interest in the Services.<br><br>**Communications**, such as the information associated with your requests or inquiries, including for support, assistance, or order information, and any feedback you provide when you communicate with us. |
| F. Internet or Network Activity | **Online activity information**, such as the website you visited before browsing to the Service, pages or screens you viewed, time spent on a page or screen, navigation paths between pages or screens, information about your activity on a page or screen, access times, and duration of access.<br><br>**Device information**, such as your computer or mobile device operating system type and version number, wireless carrier, manufacturer and model, browser type, screen resolution, IP address, unique identifiers, general location information such as city, state, or geographic area, and information about the device’s interaction with our Services. |
| G. Professional or Employment-Related Information | **Professional information**, such as company name, title, company location, business contact information, and other details we may collect about your business or profession. |
| H. Inferences Drawn from Personal Information | **Profiles** reflecting your preferences, characteristics, predispositions, or behavior, such as a billing activity and payment patterns. |

Personal Information does not include de-identified information that cannot reasonably identify, relate to, describe, be capable of being associated with, or be linked, directly or indirectly, to a particular individual, and for which BillGO has implemented technical safeguards and business processes that prohibit reidentification of the individual. BillGO commits to maintain and use such information in its de-identified form and not attempt to reidentify such information.

We may obtain personal information about you from a variety of sources, including:

* * **Personal Information that You Provide**. We collect the personal information that you provide to us, such as when you fill in forms on our Website, use BillGO Services, register to use our Services, subscribe to our Services, post material, request further Services, communicate with us, participate in our surveys, or complete transactions through the Services.  

    * **Personal Information Collected Automatically**. We, our service providers, and our advertising partners may automatically log or collect personal information about you, your computer, or your mobile device, and your activity over time on the Services and on other sites and online services, such as the online activity information and device information described in the table above. The technologies we may use for this automatic data collection may include:   
         
        * * **Cookies (or browser cookies)**. A cookie is a small file placed on a user’s device to uniquely identify the user’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser for the purpose of helping the user navigate between pages efficiently, remembering preferences, enabling functionality, helping us understand user activity and patterns, and facilitating online advertising. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. If you select this setting, however, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Services. Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Services. Cookies may be used for session management, including the storage of device identifiers.
            * **Flash Cookies**. Certain features of our Services may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Services. Flash cookies are used for purposes similar to cookies but allow storage of a larger amount of data. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.
            * **Web Beacons**. Pages of the Services or our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit BillGO, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).
            * **Session-Replay Technologies**. We may use third-party software in some locations of the Services to record a video replay of users’ interactions with the Services. The video replay may include users’ clicks, mouse movements, scrolls, mobile app touches, typing, and other activity taken during the session. We use these replays for research and development purposes, such as to help us troubleshoot problems with the Services, understand how users interact with and use the Services, and identify areas for improvement.
            * **SDKs**. Software development kits (SDKs) are software components we may use in the App for a variety of purposes, such as to provide us with analytics regarding your use of our Services, integrate with third-party platforms, add features or functionality to our Services, or facilitate online advertising. SDKs may enable third parties to collect information directly about you through the App.  

    * **Personal Information from Third Parties.** We may also collect personal information about you from third parties, including but not limited to third-party verification services, credit bureaus, entities that you connect to the Services (such as billers, retailers, banks or other financial entities), mailing list providers and other advertising partners, social media platforms, publicly available sources, our affiliates and related companies, and companies that provide us with personal information to supplement what we already know about our customers and clients or to help us identify new customers or clients. We may merge or combine such personal information with the other types of personal information we collect about you.  

    * **Referrals.** Users of the Services may have the opportunity to refer colleagues, friends, or other contacts to us and share their contact information with us.  Users may not refer someone to us or share their contact information with us unless they have their permission to do so.

**Use of Personal Information**

We may use personal information for the purposes set forth below and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection:

* * **To Provide the Services**. We may use personal information about you to provide the Services and operate our business, such as to:
        * * deliver the information and support you request, including receipts, technical notices, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
            * create, manage, monitor, and maintain your account on the Services;
            * verify your identity;
            * provide you with information, products or services that you request from us;
            * fulfill any other purpose for which you provide personal information;
            * provide you with notices about your account, including expiration, renewal or change in terms notices;
            * monitor and improve your experience on the Services;
            * process your transactions, submit your payments, and monitor the status of your payments or accounts;
            * enable security features of the Services, such as by sending you authentication codes via SMS;
            * provide any contests, surveys, sweepstakes, or other promotions you participate in
            * operate our webinars and other events; and
            * contact you by phone, email, or other form of communication.

* * **Research and Development**. We may use your information for research and development purposes, including to study and improve the Services and our business, understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our users, and develop new features, functionality, products, and services. As part of these activities, we may create aggregated, de-identified, or other anonymous data from personal information we collect. We make personal information into anonymous data by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We may use this anonymous data and share it with third parties for our lawful business purposes.  

    * **Direct Marketing**. We may send you BillGO-related or other direct marketing communications as permitted by law. You may opt-out of our marketing communications as described in the “Your Choices” section below.  

    * **Interest-Based Advertising.** We work with third-party advertising companies and social media companies to help us advertise our business and to display ads for our products and services. These companies may use cookies and similar technologies over time to collect information about you (including the online activity information and device information described above in the section called “Personal Information Collected Automatically”). Such companies may use that information to serve ads that they think will interest you. In addition, some of these companies may use hashed customer lists that we share with them to deliver ads to you and to similar users on their platforms. You can learn more about your choices for limiting interest-based advertising in the “Your Choices” section below.  

    * **To Comply with Laws and Regulations**. We will use your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities.  

    * **For Compliance, Fraud Prevention, and Safety**. We may use and share your personal information to:

* * * * perform authentication and compliance activities related to the Services, such as conducting background checks, verifying identify, performing risk assessments, and filing relevant documents;
            * comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process (such as to respond to requests from government authorities);
            * maintain the safety, security, and integrity of our Services, products and services, business, databases and other technology assets;
            * protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims);
            * audit our internal processes for compliance with legal and contractual requirements and internal policies;
            * enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Services; and
            * prevent, identify, investigate and deter fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity, including cyberattacks and identity theft.

* * **With Your Consent**. In some cases we may specifically ask you for your consent to collect, use, or share your personal information, such as when required by law.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

We may share personal information about you with the entities and individuals listed below or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection:

* * **Our Subsidiaries and Affiliates**. We may share personal information with our affiliates, subsidiaries, and other related companies. For example, we may share your personal information with our related companies to provide our products and services to you, where other companies within our group perform components of the full service offering.  

    * **Service Providers**. We share personal information with our contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business or to perform functions on our behalf. For example, we work with service providers that help us perform identity verification and background checks, website hosting, maintenance, fraud monitoring, database management, cloud storage, web analytics, billing, email and SMS services, payment processing, marketing, advertising, and other purposes.  

    * **Banks and Other Financial Entities**. Depending on your use of the Services, we may share your personal information with banks and other financial entities, including in order to facilitate payments, verify the existence and condition of your account, and to confirm your authority to use a bank account.  

    * **Services Integration Partners and other Users of the Services**. We may share your personal information with other integration partners or users that participate in the Services. For example, if you use the Services to submit payments, your personal information will be shared with the billers and other entities involved in your payment transactions.  

    * **Law Enforcement, Government Authorities, and Private Parties**. Under certain circumstances, we may disclose personal information to law enforcement, government authorities, and other parties if required to do so by law or to comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request. We may also disclose personal information to these parties if we believe such action is necessary or appropriate to enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes, and for the other purposes described above in the section titled “Compliance, Fraud Prevention, and Safety.” This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and risk management.  

    * **Business Transaction Participants**. We may disclose personal information to third parties, such as a buyer or other successor, in connection with any transaction (or potential transaction) involving a merger, acquisition, consolidation, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of BillGO’s assets or business, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by BillGO about our users is among the assets transferred.  

    * **User-Directed Parties.** We will disclose your personal information in accordance with your prior consent or direction.  

    * **Professional Advisors**. We may share your personal information with persons, companies, or professional firms providing BillGO advice, consulting, auditing, and other internal business purposes, such as data analysis, auditing, accounting, tax, financial, debt collection, and legal compliance.  

    * **Advertising Partners**. We may also share personal information collected about you with third parties who we partner with for advertising campaigns or that collect information about your activity on the Services for the advertising purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

**Links to Other Sites and Services**

BillGO is not responsible for any practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor their information or content. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. Additionally, some content or applications, including advertisements, on or through the Services are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

**Your Choices**

In this section, we describe the rights and choices that may be available to our users.

* * **Update, Correct, or Delete Account Information**. You may update, delete, or correct information about yourself by accessing your account or portal within the Services, by filling out this [form](https://preferences.billgo.com/privacy), or by emailing us at [privacy@billgo.com](mailto:privacy@billgo.com).  

    * **Opt-Out of Promotional Email Communications**. You may opt out of marketing-related emails by following the opt-out or unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email, or by contacting us as described below. You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails.  

    * **Opt-Out of Text Messages**. We may offer communications via SMS texts or similar technology sent by BillGO or our service providers, such as when we send you text messages for customer service, account-related, or marketing purposes. Message and data rates may apply for these services. You may opt-out of texts by following the instructions for the applicable texting program you enroll in or by emailing us your request and mobile telephone number to [privacy@billgo.com](mailto:privacy@billgo.com). Please note, opt-outs may not apply to certain features of the Services which require us to send text messages, such as when we send authentication codes via text to help maintain the security of your account.  

    * **Third Party Platforms**. If you choose to connect the Services with a third party platform, you may have the ability to limit the information that we obtain from the third party at the time you create your account. You may also be able to control our access to your personal information through your account settings with the third party platform. Please note, if you withdraw our ability to access certain information from a third party platform, that choice will not apply to information that we have already received from that third party.  

    * **Cookies**. Most browsers let you remove or stop accepting cookies from the websites you visit. To do this, follow the instructions in your browser’s settings. Many browsers accept cookies by default until you change your settings. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all functionality of the Services, and our Website may not work properly. For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your browser and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).  

    * **Advertising Choices**. You can limit the use of your personal information for interest-based advertising by blocking third-party cookies in your browser settings, using browser plug-ins or extensions, or using your mobile device settings to limit the use of the advertising ID associated with your mobile device. You can also opt out of interest-based ads from companies participating in the following industry opt-out programs by visiting the linked websites: the Network Advertising Initiative ([http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)) and the Digital Advertising Alliance ([optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/)). Users of our App may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising in mobile apps through participating members of the Digital Advertising Alliance by installing the AppChoices mobile app, available at [https://youradchoices.com/appchoices](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices), and selecting the user’s choices. Some of the companies we work with may offer their own opt-out mechanisms, such as Google. You can learn more about how Google uses cookies for advertising purposes by clicking [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) and opt-out of ad personalization by Google by clicking [here](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en)

Many of the opt-out preferences described in this section must be set on each device or browser for which you want them to apply. Please note that some of the advertising companies we work with may not participate in the opt-out mechanisms described above, so even after opting-out, you may still receive interest-based ads from other companies. If you opt-out of interest-based advertisements, you will still see advertisements online but they may be less relevant to you.

* * **Do Not Track**. Some browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).  

    * **Declining to Provide Information.** We need to collect personal information to provide certain services. If you do not provide the information requested, we may not be able to provide those services.

**Children**

Our Services are not intended for anyone under the age of 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on or through our Services. If you are a parent or guardian or otherwise believe we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 16, please contact us (see contact information below) so that we can delete the child’s information.

**Security**

We maintain physical, electronic, and operational procedures that are designed to safeguard the security of your personal information. While we have taken commercially appropriate and required efforts to guard your personal information, we cannot guarantee that your personal information may not be accessed or disclosed accidentally or wrongfully. You acknowledge and agree that any personal information you provide or store through the Services is at your own risk. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (e.g., if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us as detailed below.    

**Transfer of Personal Information**

BillGO is headquartered in the United States, and we may work with service providers in the United States and potentially other countries. Your personal information may be collected, used, and stored in these countries or other locations outside of your home country. Privacy laws in the locations where we handle your personal information may not be as protective as the privacy laws in your home country. By providing your personal information, where applicable law permits, you hereby specifically and expressly consent to such transfer and processing and the collection, use, and disclosure set forth herein or in any applicable terms of service.

**For Nevada Residents**

WE ARE PROVIDING YOU THIS NOTICE UNDER NEVADA STATE LAW. YOU MAY BE PLACED ON OUR INTERNAL DO NOT CALL LIST OR YOU MAY REQUEST TO EXERCISE YOUR “SALE” OPT-OUT RIGHTS UNDER NEVADA REVISED STATUTES CHAPTER 603A BY EMAILING US AT [privacy@billgo.com](mailto:privacy@billgo.com) OR WRITING TO US USING THE CONTACT INFORMATION AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**For Vermont Residents**

UNDER VERMONT LAW, WE WILL NOT SHARE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT VERMONT RESIDENTS UNLESS THE LAW ALLOWS.

Pursuant to Vermont Regulation B-2018-01, BillGO MT, Inc. does not share nonpublic personal information it collects about Vermont residents outside of our subsidiaries and affiliated companies unless legally permitted. For example, with your consent, we may share Vermont resident information to maintain your account or pursuant to joint marketing agreements with financial institutions with which we have executed agreements. Additionally, with your consent, we may share information about your creditworthiness with our subsidiaries and affiliated companies; however, we may share information about your transactions or our experiences with you with our subsidiaries and affiliated companies without your consent.

**For California Residents**

This section applies only to California residents. It describes how we collect, use, and share personal information of California residents when we act as a “business” as defined under California privacy laws, and their rights with respect to their personal information. For purposes of this section, “personal information” has the meaning given under California privacy laws but does not include information exempted from the scope of such laws. In some cases we may provide a different privacy notice to certain categories of California residents, in which case that notice will apply instead of this section.

**Personal** **Information That We Collect, Purposes of Collection and Use, and Disclosures, “Sales,” and “Sharing” of Personal Information**

We describe the categories of personal information we collect and may have collected about you in the preceding 12 months, and the categories of sources from which we collect such personal information, in the section above called “Personal Information We Collect.”

The specific business and commercial purposes for which we collect and use this information are described in the section above called “Use of Personal Information.” To the extent that we collect personal information that qualifies as “sensitive” under California privacy laws, we only use or disclose it for purposes permitted under those laws (e.g., to perform the Services, detect security incidents and prevent fraud, and to verify and maintain the quality of the Services). We do not collect or use sensitive personal information for the purpose of inferring characteristics about California residents.

**Personal Information Disclosed for Business Purposes, “Sold,” or “Shared”**

Each category of personal information listed above may be disclosed, and has in the preceding 12 months been disclosed to the categories of third parties set out in the section above called “Sharing of Personal Information” for the business purposes described in the Privacy Policy, such as to provide the Services or for research and development.

In addition, when we provide personal information to certain third parties or permit them to automatically collect personal information on the Services (such as our advertising partners like Google), California privacy laws may define this type of disclosure as a “sale” or “sharing” of personal information. Specifically, when we “sell” personal information, that means we are disclosing a California resident’s personal information to a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration. When we disclose personal information to third parties for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising, whether or not for monetary or other valuable consideration, it qualifies as “sharing” under California law.

We may “sell” or “share,” and in the preceding twelve months may have “sold” or “shared,” (1) Individual Identifiers, and (2) Internet or Network Activity, in each case for purposes of advertising our Services, identifying new customers or potential customers, and the other purposes described above under the section titled “Use of Personal Information.” We do not knowingly “sell” or “share” the personal information of California residents under 16 years of age.

**Retention of Personal Information**

We will retain each of the categories of personal information listed above for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose of collection, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, to establish and defend legal claims, for fraud prevention purposes, or as long as required to meet our legal obligations. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information, the purposes for which we process your personal information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California privacy law provides California residents with the rights listed below. Please note, these rights are not absolute and in some cases we may not be able to respond to your request, such as when a legal exemption applies or if we are not able to verify your identity.

* * **Right to Access/Know**. You have the right to request certain information about our collection and use of your personal information, including:
        * * The categories of personal information we have collected about you.
            * The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected.
            * The business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing personal information.
            * The categories of third parties to whom we disclose personal information.
            * The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
    * **Right to Delete.** You have the right to request to delete personal information that we have collected from you, subject to certain exceptions.
    * **Right to Correct.** You have the right to request us to correct inaccurate personal information that we maintain about you.
    * **Right to Opt-Out of Sales or Sharing**. If we “sell” or “share” your personal information, you can opt-out.
    * **Right to Nondiscrimination**. You are entitled to exercise the rights described above without receiving discriminatory treatment.

* * **Access/Know, Deletion, or Correction Rights**. To exercise the access/know, deletion, or correction rights described above, please submit a request to us and provide the information we request that is required to verify your request by:
        * * Filling out this [form](https://preferences.billgo.com/privacy), or,
            * Calling us at +1-844-328-3520.
    * **Right to Opt-Out of the “Sale” or “Sharing” of Personal Information**. Under California law, some of the data we share with our advertising partners may qualify as a “sale” or “share” as defined under California law. To exercise your right to opt-out of such “sale” or “sharing”, please:
        * * Email us at privacy@billgo.com, or
            * Click here: [Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information.](https://preferences.billgo.com/dont_sell)

When exercising your rights or otherwise assisting you, we may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity. This is a security measure to ensure we do not, for example, disclose personal information to any person who is not entitled to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response. The identity verification process may vary based on the type of request and how it is submitted.

You may also designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. If you do so, we may require your proof of identification, the authorized agent’s proof of identification, and any other information that we may request in order to verify your request, including evidence of valid permission for the authorized agent to act on your behalf.

Please note, we will not be able to process your request if you do not provide us with sufficient detail to allow us to understand and respond to it.

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal information (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee or decline to comply with your request if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive, or excessive.

**“Shine the Light” Requests**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.83, California residents are entitled to ask us, once per year, for a notice identifying the categories of information which we share with our affiliates or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates or third parties.  Requests will apply to information provided during the previous calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to: privacy@billgo.com with the subject heading: “California Shine the Light Request” or to BillGO, Inc,  3003 E. Harmony Rd., 5th floor, Fort Collins, CO 80528 (Attn: Privacy).

**California Notice of Financial Incentive**

We may offer certain financial incentive programs that can result in different price, rate, level, or quality of goods or services, provided that such programs are reasonably related to the value of your personal information to us. For example, we may offer additional content to users who sign up for our mailing list, or giveaways, sweepstakes, contests, or other similar promotional campaigns. We typically ask you to provide your email address or other contact information in order to participate in these programs or campaigns.

We offer these programs and campaigns because, among other things, the value of your personal information to us is related to the value of the free or discounted services, or other benefits that you obtain or that are provided as part of the applicable program or campaign. This value is based on the expense related to offering those services and benefits to participants, along with other factors such as whether and to what extent you take advantage of (or opt-out from) any offerings and whether we are able to use the data we collect from you.

When we offer any program or campaign, there is no obligation to opt-in, and you may withdraw at any time by contacting us using the designated method set forth in the applicable program rules or in the “Contacting Us” section below. Please review the applicable program or campaign offering or terms to view full details, including how to join.

**Contact Information**

Please contact us with any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or the Services provided at [Privacy@billgo.com](mailto:Privacy@billgo.com) or BillGO, Inc, 3003 E. Harmony Rd., 5th floor, Fort Collins, CO 80527 (Attn: Privacy).

© 2024 BillGO, Inc. All rights reserved.

Certain products and services offered are provided by BillGO MT, Inc. NMLS#2005089  
Phone: +1 (800) 457-3682
